thisisuntrackable: hi
Crannigan: Hey I'm new to the stream
lil_cheet0: <3
Crannigan: decided to follow you on a youtube binge earlier :)
lil_cheet0: shamaDab shamaKiss
coProof: BCash?
coProof: how much will the transaction be
LeviStreams: lol @Crannigan
Crannigan: monkaS @LeviStreams
Crannigan: needed something to watch while finishing my genetic algo
coProof: what are transactions fees these days?
LeviStreams: commanaiarchive kept popping up in my youtube recommendations
Bryanswagbeast: Eh!
moreningwould: same
Bryanswagbeast: whats he up to?
crazyserb011: I was watching an older video on youtube :D
quillford: can you check my speed challenge?
suurrend3r: hiii
LeviStreams: great content to binge for sure
coProof: are you doing bcash or bitcoin
suurrend3r: I know you won't use brave for a long time
suurrend3r: the same thing you did with Startpage xD
coProof: can you make a bitconnect transaction from scratch plz?
ThatGuyChaos: Thoughts on Coinbase CEO saying they’re going to be “the next Wells Fargo”? Seems like he doesn’t understand the point of crypto is to not have have massive centralization hubs
spellwish: how come you use iOS and not linux or windows
Bryanswagbeast: lol what are u about to hack? -_-
Bryanswagbeast: ninjaCreep mthGrin
coProof: MAC OSX
abstractingagent: YES GEORGE WHAT'S GOOD HOMIE
crazyserb011: hahah
Crannigan: fuck politics
coProof: can you make the transaction dependent on rsi crossover?
ThatGuyChaos: @ me bro
Bryanswagbeast: ill donate if you teach us a little bit of hacking!
ViktorTV: @tomcr00s3 are you by any chance looking for interns are would even consider having an intern?
bjornswife: just just coinbase bruh
Mac_33: I'm supposed to be working on class assignments, but I'd rather implement AI-denoising for my renderer instead
littlebighead82: what the point of using SHA-256 encryption Kappa
Jewishrambo: Yo
coProof: rand(1,100)
Mac_33: what happened to 'fuck chrome' Kappa
Mac_33: check out ungoogled-chromium
kkuette: I hate google but tensorflow's fine :D
Bryanswagbeast: Reverse Engineering? @tomcr00s3
coProof: why is it not changing
bjornswife: yoink
bjornswife: bitcoin cash is not bitcoin
Bryanswagbeast: lmao
crazyserb011: I told everyone on facebook that i'm not voting they all got offended
coProof: yeah no dont worry i wont touch the BCH chain
Mac_33: Do you have a public twitter acct?
ViktorTV: @tomcr00s3 would you by any chance have an intern at comma?
bjornswife: imagine using facebook in 2018 lul
Crannigan: if I told my dad i don't vote he'd have a heart attack @crazyserb011
coProof: ourselves
Bryanswagbeast: if you can track where i live, ill believe u! @tomcr00s3
Jewishrambo: Do math ourselves
littlebighead82: bch DansGame
LeviStreams: hotz, when you gonna do a from the transistor stream?
Mac_33: ripemd160 is a shorter hash used for the address string
quillford: cheer1
crazyserb011: I find it funny. they don't care who i vote for just that i do
coProof: Mac sounds correct
littlebighead82: why is that funny lul
bjornswife: do your public duty and vote for trump
crazyserb011: hahha
coProof: right after I buy some BCH
Mac_33: If I don't forget, ripemd160 is then converted to base58 for the presentable public keystring
Bryanswagbeast: #fuckTrump
bjornswife: hotz wants to build the wall
Mac_33: base58 because they wanted to take out some similar chars like O->0
crazyserb011: not into politics.
littlebighead82: how old r u
Mac_33: I actually tried writing a cryptocurrency in Swift
crazyserb011: 26
littlebighead82: and u don't care who makes the laws?
crazyserb011: it's all the same
coProof: can the private key be randomly generated from your toy slam algo?
bjornswife: replace politicians with smart contracts
crazyserb011: the 1% make the laws
littlebighead82: big yikes
Bryanswagbeast: do you still need money for rice? lol! @tomcr00s3
bjornswife: poggers
Mac_33: Hotz, we should automate governance.
Jeppelelle: Dude, come on, close the update notification RuleFive
bjornswife: use tezos
crazyserb011: ios want's an update
coProof: Updates Ready to Install
revler1: i like money :)
bjornswife: give this millionaire your bitcoins
coProof: zqr
bjornswife: hurry
glitchedoutt: Are bitcoins still useful to purchase?
littlebighead82: gotta love open source
Bryanswagbeast: wait... were u serious? r u teaching us how to hack? @tomcr00s3
coProof: hurry up
Bryanswagbeast: for white hat hackers?
Mac_33: Do you even ethereum
sfmoose: this is where geo hot looses his bitcoin live
coProof: if this was ethereum i'd send you some but no
littlebighead82: Ethereum Kreygasm Kreygasm
Mac_33: Up next: we wait 45 minutes for the transaction to confirm
bjornswife: dont trust us
sfmoose: STEALING IT NOW
coProof: that sounds like a challenge
littlebighead82: downloading the main frame now
quillford: cheer1
revler1: i am a noob :(
sfmoose: BCH PLZ
coProof: i'm gonna need to donwload a little more ram if i run that
crazyserb011: and it's gone
unctarheelss: no 1080
bjornswife: seed=1337
crazyserb011: https://imgur.com/gallery/lcxyE0D
coProof: most common seed therefore easiest to be haxed
brandoncode: do you go live every day?
sfmoose: does comma ai not provide enough work for you?
sfmoose: sorry no speaky of it again
sfmoose: audio is fantastic
quillford: audio is fine
pugs0n: audio is fine
Jewishrambo: This stream is scuffed.
Crannigan: what if I really am fucked?
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: comma ai confirmed dead PepeHands
sfmoose: audio is great dont fuck with it
808kid: Audio is fine
Jewishrambo: Is he drunk ? What you drinking ?
littlebighead82: "You're fucked. That's right!" LUL
Mac_33: Are you intoxicated? I see you're only typing at 200WPM...
sfmoose: play us something in Hungarian minor on the keyboard
coProof: No one wants yur bch
littlebighead82: bch is like dirt to us Tom
sfmoose: yeah do 480 or higher
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: D:
coProof: You’d have to pay me to take your BCH
crazyserb011: hahah
crazyserb011: ban
Crannigan: pwned
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: Geohot booli D:
sfmoose: LOL
brandoncode: Audio is very good
Jewishrambo: PogChamp
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
Crannigan: audio is much nice
littlebighead82: lol coProof
LeviStreams: lol
unctarheelss: dictatorship
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: cash.coin.dance LULW
crazyserb011: on to youtube
glitchedoutt: audio is awesome (gulp)
Jewishrambo: Audio is good BibleThump don’t hurt me
crazyserb011: lol
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: lol well it was a fun stream
ThatGuyChaos: Lol
glitchedoutt: heil audio
Crannigan: LOL ^
Jeppelelle: Why not just start a normal bank and then just put 393 billion into your account balance
bjornswife: roger ver made you
suurrend3r: say a guy who streams once a month
Bryanswagbeast: yeah the stream is over and he will hack u!
suurrend3r: did you ever try a git alternative?
ThatGuyChaos: What’s the over/under on minutes until someone steals it
coProof: Yeah pls integrate twitchslam here
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: exbosed
crazyserb011: he will hack your moms pacemaker then what
Jewishrambo: Exposed
bjornswife: lol
brandoncode: what time is it where you live?
littlebighead82: take his bch and he will hack ur amygdala
minhazm: Git amend and force push
bjornswife: that was quick
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: @tomcr00s3 Are pop tarts sandwiches? 🤔
SnakeOneMLG: VoHiYo
coProof: Git push origin master
suurrend3r: did you ever try a git alternative @tomcr00s3 ?
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: D:
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: SO MEAN
KhanDesi: lol
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
bjornswife: fake
sfmoose: please show the private key so we know you're public key matches.
suurrend3r: LUL
KhanDesi: ^
KhanDesi: we must verify
Jewishrambo: Use vscode I plen
sfmoose: it's the only way
Jewishrambo: Use vscode pleb
KhanDesi: @sfmoose damn, you subbed, but there's no emotes for this channel
KhanDesi: that's either dedication or desperation
coProof: @jewishrambo is right
SnakeOneMLG: is the audio broken for you aswell chat?
KhanDesi: @SnakeOneMLG no
pugs0n: AUDIO IS FINE
Mac_33: I have a screencap of your privkey, but I feel merciful tonight.
SnakeOneMLG: hmmm 🤔
Jok4ndre: https://clips.twitch.tv/ArbitraryEnchantingWolfBloodTrail
crazyserb011: Microsoft bought git. how do you feel about that
quillford: no they bought github
bjornswife: basically same thing tho...
crazyserb011: wow
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: ":Microsoft bought git "🤔
ThatGuyChaos: Definitely not the same thing
SnakeOneMLG: hmmm interesting, when I have quality on 360p the audio is completelly broken but on 480p it is normal
weedlord666: git===github
pugs0n: solution: don't use 360p
SnakeOneMLG: B)
Mac_33: sell toaster, buy internet
Jok4ndre: git == github?
SnakeOneMLG: git = github
Mac_33: Just as I sent that, my player downgraded to 360p
SnakeOneMLG: haa
SnakeOneMLG: haha
kkuette: Please just check git wiki page
KhanDesi: git != github
kkuette: you'll see
Jeppelelle: you guys sitting on toaster internet speeds?
KhanDesi: gitlab > github
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: @tomcr00s3 Was JS a mistake? 🤔
bjornswife: bitbucket andy
Mac_33: Endianness - Fucken computers, amirite?
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: D:
brandoncode: don't like youtube to stream?
KhanDesi: JS = John Swick
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: jon snow
Jewishrambo: JavaScript u noob
Jebbbbbbbbbbb: JS = Jour Smom Kappa
sfmoose: Jet Ski
KhanDesi: jon snow dies
KhanDesi: snape kills him
glitchedoutt: jamba shake
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: NotLikeThis
RenderMonkey: python 3 was a mistake!
KhanDesi: Jebaited
coProof: Just do a Tripp’s handshake and yur good
sfmoose: time to just use BTC
Mac_33: Do you have an opinion of the Swift language?
Jok4ndre: is there a python 1?
KhanDesi: yes
KhanDesi: it's a snek
coProof: This is good bedtime material
suurrend3r: that's some clean code
FalconJet_: what keyboard do you have?
sfmoose: I can't wait until he goes to send and the wallet is empty and he just RAGE QUITS
OMG_STD: @tomcr00s3 have you used Go or rust? Any opinion on either?
Bryanswagbeast: dont know what type but he mentioned a mechanical keyboard with no letters
sfmoose: @FalconJet_ just buy Ergo Ez Dock and call it a day
KhanDesi: how he type letters if keyboad have no letters
sfmoose: ErgoDox EZ
Jeppelelle: Guys, build a dactyl keyboard, thank me later
Mac_33: @KhanDesi Whatever the opposite of hunt-and-peck is I suppose.
KhanDesi: hunted-and-pecked
glitchedoutt: what's dactyl
Jok4ndre: what is he doing?
Mac_33: Sending fake bitcoins from one address to another
littlebighead82: 80 viewers POGGERS
Mac_33: With raw python3
sfmoose: WIN A JET SKI!
KhanDesi: Yo, who wants to send me like $300, I gotta put my team together for DreamHack Atlanta. #BrownWall
suurrend3r: b'' for what?
Mac_33: Why are you not writing this in x86 assembly my dude?
coProof: Okay going to bed. I expect my wallet to have 30 BCH in it by am.
ViktorTV: @suurrend3r byte
KhanDesi: @suurrend3r to convert to byets
suurrend3r: @ViktorTV sure
suurrend3r: thx
Targon28: just found your videos on youtube today and just watching you program is insane. How often do you stream
KhanDesi: ^ same lol
KhanDesi: I want more SLAM
Jeppelelle: Isnt the youtube channel just someone that ripped of his streams and uploaded?
suurrend3r: @Jebbbbbbbbbbb yeah
KhanDesi: yeah, sounds about right
suurrend3r: @Jeppelelle yeah xD
suurrend3r: LUL
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: i only found this stream cuz of that youtube channel tho
KhanDesi: falcatedFacts only
Mac_33: Bitcoin Cash = Fake News Bitcoin
Mac_33: As we all know, the only *real* bitcoin is Ethereum.
Mac_33: Kappa
trashcan___: at least call it by its real name
trashcan___: bcash
KhanDesi: the only real crypto is KhanDesium, please send it to me
Bryanswagbeast: just give yourself 1000 bitcoins! @tomcr00s3
Jok4ndre: i also come from that channel.
sfmoose: Yeah youtube is how I found this channel as well. Binge watched the archive.
Mac_33: The script part is a bit annoying to implement tbh
KhanDesi: you binge watched a bunch of 10 hour streams?
Mac_33: You need OP_CHECKSIG at least
Mac_33: You need to gather inputs and form a new output, append script and sig
Mac_33: And S E N D
Mac_33: You literally just send the shit to the node
Mac_33: *in the correct format
Mac_33: Ah yeah, handshake first
Mac_33: You can just broadcast the TX, if it's valid it'll be accepted by the nodes
SnakeOneMLG: !uptime
Jok4ndre: no bots
Mac_33: I believe TX witness is for the newer type of txn
Mac_33: SEGWIT
Mac_33: Google it
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: i just did 3 politics tho
CharlieKelly_aka_Dayman: ok thanks! ill try that
un3okapi: guys, how do I git gud like geohot?
suurrend3r: WutFace WutFace
Targon28: Tips on learning even 1/100th of what you know? lol
suurrend3r: I think hotz is drinking too much enery drinks
kkuette: Google it ?
SnakeOneMLG: He is just very good at working with little information
trashcan___: i think its a spindrift
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL
SnakeOneMLG: monkaS
suurrend3r: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
Mac_33: What are you on
suurrend3r: Cocaine and Python
Mac_33: You can ask other nodes for key balance
Mac_33: You do not need to sync the chain. You're creating a light node
Mac_33: getreceivedbyaddress
Nagato_Pain: heyyy
Mac_33: May not be the right one
Mac_33: Like, you need to get the inputs for your address
Mac_33: And then count up the satoshis
Mac_33: Since you only have 1 txn, you just use that amount
suurrend3r: do you like Ruby hotz?
Mac_33: Yeah I noticed that, my bad!
Mac_33: I'm sure you could ping some service for the balance!
Mac_33: If you don't want to use other nodes, you *have* to sync the blockchain
Mac_33: I guess you could only sync the last 100 or so blocks for this purpose
Mac_33: You just request the blocks from other nodes
Mac_33: I think you could just ping a full BTC node for the balance too, and rely on that data
Mac_33: Yeah there's no protocol call for getting balance, since an address doesn't have a balance, you have to read the ledger to figure out the "balance"
quillford: is this blockchain for sensorless openpilot?
Mac_33: You really just want to download blocks, find the single input to your old address, and use that to form a new output to send
Mac_33: Important: Nodes may ban you if you don't follow the protocol properly
Mac_33: So make sure to ping different nodes
Mac_33: Are you trying a random node each time?
Mac_33: You are, yeah
honeybadger_____: do u have a full time job or used to?
un3okapi: comma.io
Jeppelelle: hes working for Sony
Jeppelelle: ;)
PENK4: 1080p please
CharlieTLe: Hi George, was just watching your SLAM video!
scriptedp0ison_: im hyped
suurrend3r: EleGiggle EleGiggle EleGiggle
suurrend3r: PJSugar PJSugar
Mac_33: Have you gotten any response? Network byte order?
scriptedp0ison_: how do i become a part of google project zero?
Mac_33: You find 10 0days in 10 hours, and then send a tweet to sergey. Then the ritual will begin.
scriptedp0ison_: lol
Mac_33: What are you doing differently now apart from the call? Try version again?
kimmilol: LUL
Mac_33: DAMNIT
Crannigan: Kappa
suurrend3r: daaaammnnn
Jeppelelle: hahhahah
Mac_33: That's lame as fuck
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
scriptedp0ison_: seriously?
OPHaru: LUL
akalioceania: clip it boys
honeybadger_____: i hope u didnt lose alot lol
suurrend3r: for real?
abadonna6: EZ
Jeppelelle: who was it, confess guys
sfmoose: fuck man I just shit myself
Mac_33: That reaction WAS priceless, however.
Crannigan: LOL
scriptedp0ison_: same
OPHaru: nice Jebaited
sfmoose: RAGE QUIT!
Quiplash: congrats u played urself
Boblikesdoritos: The bitcoins are safe!
akalioceania: https://clips.twitch.tv/FurryGlamorousLousePipeHype
ThatGuyChaos: Lol
sfmoose: This stream is amazing
scriptedp0ison_: hype
ThatGuyChaos: Spindrift shill
Mac_33: Hotz, I challenge you to a Type-off
sfmoose: 23
sfmoose: i bad at math
Mac_33: Tomorrow, the internet. Be there.
Jeppelelle: Forget about this bitcoin crap, just create a new cryptocurrency that mines with the tp:s from SLAM
ThatGuyChaos: When’s the spindrift ICO
scriptedp0ison_: B)
trashcan___: right after the lacroix ico
Mac_33: Bitcoin will end world hunger.
Mac_33: Everybody says so.
scriptedp0ison_: George you don't use cake?
scriptedp0ison_: cake browser
Mac_33: ungoogled-chromium is neat
Mac_33: Also can you close that update notif in the top right
sfmoose: steven hawking loved strip clubs, google images that shit
sfmoose: need more bitcoin to cover tx fees to steal bitcoin. fuck this broke ass bastard.
scriptedp0ison_: north korea is really banging the blockchain
Mac_33: Everything you have to work with is in that one BTC protocol doc
Mac_33: If you were stephen hawking, you'd be dead.
gofaq: Hello... What are best choice: python or clojure?
scriptedp0ison_: python 100% right now
sfmoose: python if you enjoy employment
gofaq: should i learn python? ok)
gofaq: i try
gunnaren: Yey - finally made it to a livestream!
gofaq: love u vids and stream
Mac_33: what music are you digginga tm
syte29: The legend geohot at it again
sfmoose: you need more bitcoin so e40
sfmoose: e40
sfmoose: e40 choices
akalioceania: play infant annihilator OMEGALUL
Quiplash: rest ez lil peepee
Mac_33: Don't you just hash the tx, sign that and append it?
syte29: I wish I had this much focus. I've been coding the past hr and still haven't produced anything noteworthy. :(
Mac_33: George, how well did you do in university?
sfmoose: That's why I don't go outside, I like to do stuff.
abadonna6: i'm good at masterbating
scriptedp0ison_: mad respect George stays grinding 💯
sfmoose: can you teach me?
jitterbug_gang: how often do you masturbate george?
syte29: George too busy putting reverse shells into bitches so he can pop it later
Jok4ndre: !song
sfmoose: he likes his tx raw
CharlieTLe: Noticed you used vim a lot, why not download the vimium plugin for chrome?
Jeppelelle: Whats the theory behind that a reverse would work?
Mac_33: Because a website said so
Jeppelelle: ok :D
syte29: He really is like the new Martin Shkreli
foxubu: Back to Chrome? :(
un3okapi: martin shkreli is irreplaceable
syte29: RIP Shkreli. He still updates his blog though :)
syte29: They do have similar personalities though
Mac_33: I forked your repo, YEBOI
scriptedp0ison_: george you ever work with opencv?
suurrend3r: it fucking works
akalioceania: is this guy on drugs?
Mac_33: This guy is on LIFE
syte29: Adderall most likely
syte29: I would like some too :)
jitterbug_gang: this is what a peak alpha male looks like
foxubu: wait till he gets neck and back problems the way he sits
5umu: hey george what are u coding
Jeppelelle: 5umu he is teaching us how to steal his bitcoins
5umu: Ah thanks
suurrend3r: he hit this high only once a month thats because he stream so irregularly
5umu: just tuned in
RedzaMusic: i love lil pump
Mac_33: Merkle root of the block
Mac_33: you can traverse that and find a given txn
scriptedp0ison_: lil peep?
foxubu: we want kitty
jitterbug_gang: hey george have you ever done DMT?
scriptedp0ison_: shes okay
suurrend3r: I hate lil pump but love geohot
Mac_33: hotz will you join my discord for COOL PEOPLE
Mac_33: I haven't created it yet, but I may if you want to join.
Mac_33: Oh I was right about SOMETHING
foxubu: Code this in Java ... Gosh Kreygasm Kreygasm
CharlieTLe: Noticed you used vim a lot, why not download the vimium plugin for chrome?
scriptedp0ison_: python is life thats why no java
foxubu: Subscribers have a longer Squid4
scriptedp0ison_: ?
foxubu: @scriptedp0ison_ true
michalmx2: u
sfmoose: hacky hacky hacky
abadonna6: where's the like button
Mac_33: and SMASH that like button
sfmoose: we love you george
gunnaren: we love u
scriptedp0ison_: were here for you george
jitterbug_gang: wholesome geohot
foxubu: we love geohot
scriptedp0ison_: lord geohot
abadonna6: i rate this broadcast 5 stars
v0lko: @CharlieTLe does that do muhc? I used to use vimperator, but it's not supported anymore
sfmoose: please play us out on that keyboard tonight. something soft so I can fall asleep.
sfmoose: yes yes
scriptedp0ison_: hype
CharlieTLe: @v0lko Yeah, it's pretty awesome. Highly recommend.
abadonna6: 2 dollars closer to a jet ski
scriptedp0ison_: ever listen to froggy fresh?
Mac_33: No ice? Just freeze some water. BAM!
sfmoose: gimme 2 dollar I make you holla
foxubu: Kitty Music Please°
foxubu: / Ty
foxubu: Ty /
CharlieTLe: I like "kasbo aldrig mer" or "martin garrix"
CharlieTLe: https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/vimium/dbepggeogbaibhgnhhndojpepiihcmeb?hl=en
foxubu: Damn he jumped out of the screen lol
scriptedp0ison_: got me dancin in my sheets
NoPartiesGuy: Guys, I have a question, what linux distro for a dev (mostly node, but python is planned also), ubuntu, fedora or manjaro. I heard ubuntu collects data, so I am sceptic to this one. I am just curious, maybe there is other distro, but I tried couple times and had certain problems, e.g. with mmy mechanical corsair keyboard. I thought this will be good place to ask, if I was wrong sorry :p
Mac_33: macOS is by far the best distro.
foxubu: Manjaro if you wanna stay update to date with packages.
scriptedp0ison_: ubuntu gives you the choice to send your usage statistics for future development. it has a far bigger user base..so when you need help its there
scriptedp0ison_: ubuntu can be configured for bleeding edge too
Mac_33: You don't have to send *all* the satoshi, you can send the excess back to yourself.
Mac_33: LAME
un3okapi: uh oh
foxubu: WTF
5umu: woww
gunnaren: what a douche
OPHaru: LUL
NoPartiesGuy: wow
quillford: if i send you bitcoins, will you check my speed challenge?
honeybadger_____: lol
Froopyland: lmao this stream
syte29: let's find that person
sfmoose: I'll send you some bitcoins, if that means the project continues
syte29: and beat 'em :(
abadonna6: we will find you and we will dismember you
gunnaren: that was our uber eats money
Bryanswagbeast: will i make your day if i donate you? @tomcr00s3
scriptedp0ison_: pull apart everyone to find the block address
NoPartiesGuy: LUL
syte29: yes :)!
tacorising3: LUL
OPHaru: time to steal 2,300 back
tomcr00s3: qq7pxh4xfyqype5nqynt4h6zxz0ma4du6cl47kva2f
scriptedp0ison_: #geohunt
JoneKone: no doxing
5umu: LOL
gunnaren: LUL
syte29: dox 'em anyway :)
xEHLE_: twitch gets really upset if you do that
Bryanswagbeast: lmao
OPHaru: TOS forsenS
notbigd: lol wild
Bryanswagbeast: Hey brother will i make your day if i sub? @tomcr00s3
michalmx2: hello George. do you know gynvael coldwind?
sfmoose: but you only had $2 something
sfmoose: not saying that was wrong
sfmoose: wasnt
JoneKone: how did he steal it?
syte29: what a dick
Bryanswagbeast: is there a way you can get his ip address ?
syte29: private key posted
syte29: what a cunt :(
scriptedp0ison_: bioluminescent cia agent took it
JoneKone: asshole
Crannigan: the private way posted for a good hour before anyone did anything though
Mac_33: Other nodes know which IP submitted the txn
abadonna6: who knew
notbigd: no surprise
scriptedp0ison_: cant you check or request the transaction ledger?
lupo1989: well if your hackimg playstation you can also to be hacked once you publish your private key xD
syte29: :O
xEHLE_: @scriptedp0ison_ is that a reference to the less PC version of that phrase from Terry Davis? LUL
honeybadger_____: lmao
OPHaru: lmao
abadonna6: lmao
syte29: which will be stolen it in a second :(
abadonna6: someones getting rich today
OPHaru: another 4usd to steal TriHard
sfmoose: how do you have a sound when it deposits?
sfmoose: that's awesome
sfmoose: you're welcome for the $4
scriptedp0ison_: lmfao maybe
Bryanswagbeast: I subbed brother!
foxubu: Send him 3 dollars back just in case
sfmoose: :)
sfmoose: i know just gotta move fast
quillford: you should just go back to twitchchess
ziggyzergling: asking for civility in twitch chat
suurrend3r: Yeah, what happened with twitchchess
suurrend3r: this is fucking cool too
Bryanswagbeast: whats twitchchess?
foxubu: @Bryanswagbeast see github.com/geohot It was a project he streamed to build neural nets for playing chess
Bryanswagbeast: ok thanks!
scriptedp0ison_: contact the BIA (blockchain intelligence agency)
eionard: !playlist
syte29: i never got my bch from the split. stupid gdax :(
scriptedp0ison_: arent those nightbot commands
syte29: geohot in mission impossible
sfmoose: still pending confirmations
foxubu: time's race #ACTION
Bryanswagbeast: lol
Bryanswagbeast: lets track that b****
syte29: dude's probably just waiting
xEHLE_: if im not fully retarded, which i may be, the stolen bitcoins got sent to the BTC donation wallet of Khan Academy
xEHLE_: at least it went to a good cause, i guess
sfmoose: good sluthing
Mac_33: I don't see it
sfmoose: I do I do
honeybadger_____: Pog
honeybadger_____: PogChamp
abadonna6: cliffhanger
JoneKone: @xEHLE_ All "non" profit organizations are a like.. like the cake
guishade: PJSalt
Bryanswagbeast: how many exploits do you currently own?
sfmoose: Slow AF
sfmoose: spin drift sounds like a race car
Mac_33: up next: we wait 45 minutes for the transaction to confirm while hotz plays us music on his piano
Bryanswagbeast: lol he took roche! you can tell since he's rubbing his nose! lol
syte29: blockchain confirmation, so fast
syte29: someone wake me up
syte29: :(
syte29: geohot you investing in EOS?
syte29: Also, https://quadency.com/ very useful :)
Mac_33: EOS is a scam
stoogethomas: bch is a scam as well
Mac_33: That's way too much
Mac_33: Like 50sat/byte is enough
eionard: LUL
Jok4ndre: fbi
sfmoose: maxLOL
gunnaren: lol
syte29: lmfao
suurrend3r: lmao
5umu: LOL
OPHaru: LUL
syte29: geohot gonna fuck you up
suurrend3r: WutFace WutFace
Bryanswagbeast: Do you own any exploits? @tomcr00s3
syte29: watch it beep again
5umu: lmao imagine
CharlieTLe: KAPOW
5umu: all of that gone
syte29: isn't there a lib for this?
syte29: lots of libs. why is he packing these transactions manually. just for torture :(?
honeybadger_____: lmao
sfmoose: So simple
Mac_33: he wants to do it by hand
Mac_33: Yeah, when you coded SLAM
syte29: ah :)
syte29: good way of learning
sfmoose: use vscode and let twitchees finish writing the code while you sip spin drifts
syte29: if he were a javascript dev, it would've just been this import * from "react-bitcoin-cash"; Sigh, no wonder js is a meme :(
Mac_33: The whole JS culture is flawed
Mac_33: "how do I append to an array?" "INSTALL J-QUERY"
syte29: Agreed, we had a kid doing frontend for us, who couldn't write a nested for loop
syte29: ...
gunnaren: @Mac_33 dont you mean "you need to make a library for that " Kappa
syte29: Or struggled to do fizzbuzz. It made me die on the inside
sfmoose: https://www.npmjs.com/package/true is my fav npm package. it returns True for you.
sfmoose: left pad is pretty good too
syte29: 100% used in a serious way
syte29: Tj Holowaychuk left for that reason :(. I love JS. I hate the community
Bryanswagbeast: what programming languages do you know? @tomcr00s3
syte29: Everything is "pull in package"
stoogethomas: I don't get why geohot would support bch makes no sense. Everyone on the bch side are marketers while the people that support btc like nick szabo and adam back are actual cryptographers...
syte29: dude wrote a validation library that validated fields based on their name. wtf... :(
Mac_33: I know there are scripts that scrape github commits for privkeys and automatically steal any coin there
Mac_33: Maybe someone has a script that tries to look for bch privkeys on twitch streams?
syte29: Ah :O. That maybe it :(
Mac_33: Public key is the key you make public
sfmoose: 1McTRkmGKV59o2Wfpqh4N1mXKypyALfCMc
syte29: Makes me sad that some dick would steal over 4 dollars
Mac_33: So the non-base58 ripemd160 key
AJCrow: what a nerd this guy.. lol
sfmoose: @stoogethomas I can only surmise that BCH was used it currently has lower average block confirmation times for a quick project like this.
Mac_33: Could just use LTC for that
Mac_33: It's identical to BTC
stoogethomas: @sfmoose Ehhh no bch has 10 minute confirmation/block times much like btc. If you wanted quicker confirmation times you could use doge or ltc
Mac_33: Save for the block time
scriptedp0ison_: nerdlife
scriptedp0ison_: were all nerds
AJCrow: yes we are
Mac_33: Yeah @tomcr00s3 why didn't you use dogecoin for this
Bryanswagbeast: how many programming languages do you know? @tomcr00s3
stoogethomas: well respect to geohot either way his been doing amazing work for years much more than anything i've done
syte29: his progress makes mine looked like shit :(
syte29: look*
Mac_33: With enough practice, you can become like him
Mac_33: @tomcr00s3 what's your vimrc like
syte29: I feel like I probably couldn't. Geohot has a lot of natural ability
syte29: :(
scriptedp0ison_: SSSsss
sfmoose: ok signing off, that was a fun one. keep up the crypto streams.
xEHLE_: 2 bucks illegally donated to khan :(
syte29: later @sfmoose
scriptedp0ison_: FBBlock
suurrend3r: getting crazy now
5umu: LOL
stoogethomas: I'd be happy to send you like $20 worth of bch
AJCrow: George of the cryptojungle
scriptedp0ison_: lmao
Mac_33: How many hours do you sleep at night?
crazyserb011: I was AFK did someone steal the money
Mac_33: Yeah, but someone sent more
stoogethomas: block explorers are usually delayed. just saying
xEHLE_: Looks like none @mac_33
Bryanswagbeast: Getters n Setters maybe? @tomcr00s3
scriptedp0ison_: after you get it setup. use argparse to turn it into a cli tool for btc transactions
stoogethomas: what language is he programming this in? python?
syte29: python
scriptedp0ison_: yea
stoogethomas: thought so
syte29: :), i like python
crazyserb011: do you know who took it. do we know
Bryanswagbeast: yes Python 3
stoogethomas: I think pythons good but I like my code separated by brackets :/
syte29: any of you guys competent with sed or awk?
crazyserb011: is he going to hack them?
suurrend3r: give me a job hotz
scriptedp0ison_: yes awk
syte29: trying to learn 'em to get better at file manipulation which i have to do a lot
xEHLE_: No, but it got sent to the donation wallet of khan academy LUL @crazyserb011
scriptedp0ison_: awk is grep for parsing field delimiters
suurrend3r: getting stuck here
slovn1k: why do u use VIM? it's supper hard to learn
suurrend3r: hard af
Bryanswagbeast: lol hey geo, roll out the Job Applications!
suurrend3r: @slovn1k nah it's easy
scriptedp0ison_: vim isn't hard to learn
crazyserb011: hack khan academy lol
syte29: I'm trying to learn the entire language right now.
syte29: Syntax feels funny :)
Bryanswagbeast: @syte29 which language?
scriptedp0ison_: yeah gonna take a few years
syte29: Awk Programming Language
scriptedp0ison_: oh nvr mind
Mac_33: @tomcr00s3 Why don't you use ed?
scriptedp0ison_: its oldddd
Mac_33: ed is the standard text editor.
vtcN_: edlin
scriptedp0ison_: nano anyone?
syte29: people use nano :O
syte29: I kid I kid :P
scriptedp0ison_: lol
Bryanswagbeast: Getters n setters!
crazyserb011: It's funny his like the only streamer that everyone is afraid to steal from lol
syte29: Trying out spacemacs right now. Learning that common lisp
scriptedp0ison_: nooooo
Mac_33: Told ya
blizz191: Add me on league when you get on :)
syte29: Everything suddenly became about functional programming all of the sudden. Presenting it like some new and revolutionary idea. Sigh
scriptedp0ison_: lisp is good for learning the programming principles
suurrend3r: just reset the router
Mac_33: I don't think the nodes share ban info
Mac_33: So try another node
Bryanswagbeast: Just hack that guy Geo! @tomcr00s3
syte29: Agreed @scriptedp0ison_ :)
suurrend3r: @Mac_33 oh yeah LUL
scriptedp0ison_: @syte29 I need to learn more of it lol, only watched the derek banas tutorial :D
Bryanswagbeast: his tutorial is trash
Bryanswagbeast: you wont learn sh**
Bryanswagbeast: try Thenewboston
syte29: Oh nice, learning it from Land Of Lisp. I have a hard time listening to video tutorials
syte29: Are they any good?
scriptedp0ison_: Derek banas goes over the core so you can build from it yourself
Bryanswagbeast: yeah thenewboston
syte29: Ah, not too long of a video. Thanks @scriptedp0ison_
Bryanswagbeast: derek makes the core in one video! it could be confusing for beginners
scriptedp0ison_: Derek banas for a quick go over. then use what you learn to build from it
syte29: Yeah, I'm really just looking for something quick
syte29: I've used other functional languages just not Lisp
scriptedp0ison_: derek goes over it fast lol youll get the hang of it
syte29: This is good :). Just skipped around throughout the video. Will watch tomorrow. Had never heard of Derek prior to this.
syte29: Also an emacs tutorial <3
scriptedp0ison_: He's a really good teacher. :)
Mac_33: You're not using multisig here dude
Mac_33: Luckily there are a lot of nodes to get banned from
scriptedp0ison_: 200 lines of code, your crazy
Nagato_Pain: read the chat @tomcr00s3
scriptedp0ison_: jk
Bryanswagbeast: lol
sfmoose: I want money
abadonna6: LUL
scriptedp0ison_: BCWarrior BCWarrior
foxubu: No, The more money you receive, the faster you have to code LOL
Mac_33: Doesn't it find a new node each time?
xEHLE_: ^
Nagato_Pain: some one explain im new here and im still noob in coding
twitchmiker: that's probably why people run local nodes on testnet to test their incomplete code ;)
scriptedp0ison_: george can you auto request a node if you get blocked
scriptedp0ison_: make a fuction to handle it
Mac_33: Code FASTER HOTZ
foxubu: CODE FASTER HOTZ LOL
Mac_33: FASTER my boi!
OPHaru: take my money :)
Mac_33: This is pretty hilarious
Tanthny: LUL
sfmoose: cracking up
scriptedp0ison_: ArsonNoSexy
syte29: at this point
syte29: it's just kind of fun to send
Mac_33: Now you need to gather all the inputs, loop thru em and add them to your output
honeybadger_____: randomly mutes
suurrend3r: focus on the finish
syte29: increase temptation for the thief :O
xEHLE_: Seems like everyone in here got bitcoins LUL
honeybadger_____: the steam randomly mutes
NoPartiesGuy: Br PogChamp PogChamp kf PogChamp st
syte29: i just bought some bch just to have him freak out
scriptedp0ison_: @mac_33 you seem really versed, its impressive
honeybadger_____: ur muted...
Mac_33: I just tried implementing a cryptocurrency from scratch
Mac_33: It's incomplete, but on my github
eionard: LUL
OPHaru: LUL
scriptedp0ison_: oh lol its too complicated for me. i dont have that much experience yet
syte29: that's pretty cool. I may try that project at some point :)
abadonna6: yoink
syte29: what language are you using @Mac_33?
syte29: Also, do you have a repo up :)
scriptedp0ison_: every time someone donates Mario hits a block...get it (blockchain joke)
Mac_33: @tomcr00s3 is it okay to post my github repo link here
syte29: pretty soon george bouta go over one of them turtles
syte29: I posted a link earlier @Mac_33 . I don't think he cares :)
scriptedp0ison_: love the stream
foxubu: Drink Mate @tomcr00s3
syte29: bedtime
syte29: goodnight peeps :)
Mac_33: @syte29 https://github.com/VKoskiv/VaporCoin
un3okapi: f.lux SeemsGood
scriptedp0ison_: later @syte29 hopefully Derek Banas can teach you
syte29: Thanks @scriptedp0ison_ . @Mac_33 , will definitely star. Looks interesting. Thanks man
scriptedp0ison_: George what gave you the innovation to create comma.ai?
quillford: what does that even mean>
quillford: ?
suurrend3r: this is depressing
Mac_33: https://xkcd.com/1728/
Nagato_Pain: guys i want learn coding should i start with python or java script ?????
Nagato_Pain: @tomcr00s3
scriptedp0ison_: python
Mac_33: You should start with x86 asm and work your way up
un3okapi: LUL
scriptedp0ison_: javascript or ecma script is for the front end development aka web pages etc
Mac_33: You have to EARN the privilege of using a compiler
Mac_33: Which input are you trying to spend?
scriptedp0ison_: lol @mac_33 i dont know about that
vtcN_: lmao start with asm...
Nagato_Pain: @scriptedp0ison_ thnx Dude
scriptedp0ison_: assembly ARM architecture is easy starting point
Nagato_Pain: @Mac_33 lol so funny
scriptedp0ison_: then you can write POS malware :D
suurrend3r: just keep trying hotz
scriptedp0ison_: trying to make an IP camera exploitation and exfiltration framework but i need to load and emulate like 20 firmware and mip architecture sets
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL
scriptedp0ison_: to try and desanitize some of the built in security methods..need to make a script to automate that
SnakeOneMLG: Is this Chrome?
sfmoose: blockchain.info
SnakeOneMLG: I thought you were using Brave
blizz191: Hotz can i make you a website ur web design skills are sub par
jotembruv: !uptime
suurrend3r: theres no bot
sfmoose: you can make a wallet with a private key at blockchain.info
Mac_33: Can you not import the privkey to your phone wallet app
sfmoose: then send the BCH elsewhere
pau1riddle: Guys, please help with a problem from a textbook. How can I represent n * (-6) with 2 shifts and 1 add/sub?
scriptedp0ison_: is this assembly?
pau1riddle: No
pau1riddle: Well, yes
vtcN_: if people do your homework for you you will never learn
pau1riddle: I know you can do n * 6. It is the same as n << 2 n << 1.
pau1riddle: But -6 I don't know.
pau1riddle: Can't use ^ or &
scriptedp0ison_: what type of register are you working with? if this is assembly? there are different opcodes for each architecture and it's mostly based on the register type
suurrend3r: we getting close to depression
Mac_33: https://i.redd.it/y59sstwfphs11.jpg
scriptedp0ison_: otherwise if not assembly, then what language
pau1riddle: C
scriptedp0ison_: ouch haven't touched C in a year
Mac_33: I've been working on a path tracer in C
Mac_33: It's a lot of fun
pau1riddle: It's just to be clever. Usually compiler does such things because shifts and addition is faster than multiplication.
Mac_33: I'm trying to train a model and add AI denoising
suurrend3r: "Nobody likes C" - Geohot
scriptedp0ison_: I stopped learning C, maybe I'll pick up when I learn reverse engineering
pau1riddle: The only reason I learn C is because books use it. And because I want to fix 2 HUGE bugs in kernel drivers.
Mac_33: i like c
scriptedp0ison_: I like C too just got lazy, i should pick up again
suurrend3r: Go GeoHot Go
scriptedp0ison_: @pau1riddle yeah i have no clue about the answer you queued, i havent been on c in ages
pau1riddle: It is not about C. It is for all languages.
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 my bro
pau1riddle: Where N is either unsigned integer or two's complement.
suurrend3r: C will die soon
Mac_33: It will not.
pau1riddle: Will be superseded by Rust and Go.
scriptedp0ison_: @suurrend3r it really wont
pitersk: so wrong
Mac_33: It is the only system implementation language that is widely used
scriptedp0ison_: the hardware your using has C built into it
pau1riddle: It will remain as assembly language.
suurrend3r: @Mac_33 C is
newtomcroose: Cool , u writing a code for bitcoin , so where is taylor swfit ?
Mac_33: Try committing C to the linux kernel
scriptedp0ison_: hell the servers that is housing Twitch has some C built into its drivers, etc
Mac_33: Every single device you use and see in the world has C code in it
scriptedp0ison_: so C is here for all..its great
Mac_33: It's not going away
scriptedp0ison_: I wonder what the B language was like
pau1riddle: But it is not evolving either.
newtomcroose: stream is lag ?
scriptedp0ison_: it doesn't need to
Mac_33: It was updated in 2011
jotembruv: stream is not lag
blackburn1911: hey
newtomcroose: come on , stream is lag :|
scriptedp0ison_: I always have to specify -std=c11 or my shared object will not compile and ill get an error. need to reconfigure gcc, did some tinkering and messed things up
lolcoolkat: no lag for me
newtomcroose: a technical guy , dirty hand ? right ?
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 do u have donation like ninja in twitch ?
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose go reverse dns lookup twitch, and check the MS response time to the ICMP echo reply, that might be your issue if the response time is really high
Mac_33: typeof(NaN) = number
Mac_33: Remember to increment transaction nonce!
newtomcroose: guys , maybe i be found dead in my apartment
PEREZthe1: @newtomcroose cool :)
scriptedp0ison_: I'm getting latency too but I'm on a cellular connection, in the middle of no where
vtcN_: lol
Bryanswagbeast: hey mac what programming languages do you know?
scriptedp0ison_: MrDestructoid
chloven: LUL
newtomcroose: :))
newtomcroose: i use assembly for everything , even AI :|
scriptedp0ison_: ouch sounds rough
newtomcroose: geo get heater :D
Bryanswagbeast: @mac_33
Mac_33: ye?
Mac_33: oh
Mac_33: Quite a few?
Mac_33: Depends on what level
newtomcroose: @Mac_33 what is your favorite food ?
Mac_33: I like me some good wings
scriptedp0ison_: waffles are best
Mac_33: I mainly use Swift and C in personal projects
scriptedp0ison_: how is IOS development?
Mac_33: Okay, haven't done much of that lately
Bryanswagbeast: I was gone for a while right now! Did they take his bitcoin again?
scriptedp0ison_: Ever touch up on Objective C?
Bryanswagbeast: swift is better
Mac_33: I can still manage it
Mac_33: But swift is more prevalent
newtomcroose: :| why people talk about programming langues too much ? just learn python and pick a project :|
pau1riddle: I came up with new revolutinary optimizarion technique based on machine learning. You build ML module into kernel, it learns on your behaviour as computer user, and then loads caches and shift, across the whole stack, even making it so that branch prediction doesn't make mistakes.
suurrend3r: @newtomcroose so freaking true
Mac_33: You can't write performant code with python
Mac_33: It's good for a quick script/prototyping
Mac_33: But I need my stuff to be fast
newtomcroose: @Mac_33 yes yes , u right . learn assembly
suurrend3r: You can write in python first and then in C
Mac_33: I'm fine with just -O3
suurrend3r: LUL
pau1riddle: Caring about programming languages is a sign of Level 1 programmer.
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose why do people use a spoon for eating oatmeal but not a spoon for spaghetti?
vtcN_: Mac_33 thoughts on jon blows language jai?
newtomcroose: ohhhhhhhhhhhh i fall a part
pau1riddle: Nobody who achived anything cared. They just did.
Bryanswagbeast: i first learned C , java and then python
pau1riddle: Others were arguing on forums and imageboards about which one is better.
newtomcroose: @scriptedp0ison_ why people need se.x toys :| ?
blackburn1911: I use php and I'm happy MVGame
un3okapi: oooooooooooooo
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose I don't know, maybe to make people like you happy?
newtomcroose: We should talking about bitcoin right now . we are not good twitches right now :|
scriptedp0ison_: lol jk
Mac_33: I mentioned that earlier!
foxubu: Give up Goerge ... You feel so tired FortBush
blackburn1911: George is a winner
newtomcroose: how can i do scam with cryptocurrency ?
Mac_33: You should google UTXO if it's not clear
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose you dont, thats how you do it
newtomcroose: be smart , do scam , be rich , get fcked . right ?
Bryanswagbeast: ninjaCreep mthGrin
foxubu: same day lays only lol
suurrend3r: TearGlove
scriptedp0ison_: PogChamp
Bryanswagbeast: mrmuff21
un3okapi: :(
scriptedp0ison_: ThunBeast
suurrend3r: monkAS
scriptedp0ison_: BrokeBack
Bryanswagbeast: SeemsGood
scriptedp0ison_: HassaanChop
suurrend3r: cmonBruh cmonBruh
scriptedp0ison_: HeyGuys
Bryanswagbeast: DrinkPurple
foxubu: Get Mate George! You look tired ^_^
blackburn1911: the stream will be saved?
Bryanswagbeast: ninjaBlank mthMad
scriptedp0ison_: NomNom
foxubu: @blackburn1911 for 7 days
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 write a code to learn how to break bitcoin hash with ML and ... . what do u think ?
Bryanswagbeast: AI
foxubu: Fuzzing
newtomcroose: naaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhh
Bryanswagbeast: You need help? Call Elon Musk! @tomcr00s3
newtomcroose: elon musk just coding in php :|
scriptedp0ison_: or just call the nsa
newtomcroose: but its crazy what u can see
chloven: LUL Chrome
blackburn1911: I know the feeling
newtomcroose: chrome . can i kill you ?
denim_lap: !uptime
newtomcroose: !uptime
denim_lap: no bot D:
newtomcroose: we hate bots :| ?
vtcN_: i've had to hot-add ram because of chrome
denim_lap: anyone having idea of upitme
denim_lap: ?
newtomcroose: who need a hero ?
scriptedp0ison_: we all do
Bryanswagbeast: yupp! Chrome sucks the rams titties
denim_lap: D:
pau1riddle: Chome is now 51% of browser market
newtomcroose: She's got me spending Oh, spending all your money on me And spending time on me She's got me spending
denim_lap: that's one way to say it
scriptedp0ison_: Chromes a RAM whore
denim_lap: ok gus
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose you have the voice of an angel
newtomcroose: @scriptedp0ison_ i wanna be taylor swift bf
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose some serious goals you got there
Bryanswagbeast: so that computer that geo has is a borrowed computer from commaai and has 4 gtx 1080 ti and probably about 8 gb of ram! LMAO
chloven: :O
scriptedp0ison_: my computer is like Chrome cum take my RAM
scriptedp0ison_: *come
denim_lap: enough with chrome already
newtomcroose: realy ? he is a genius ? should i be a genius to do scam ?
scriptedp0ison_: okay @denim_lap whatever makes you happy
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 omg its 1:58 AM :))
denim_lap: thanks :D
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose what are you talking about?
newtomcroose: @scriptedp0ison_ what going on in this chat ? :|
suurrend3r: you gotta make it work @tomcr00s3
Mac_33: i am falling asleep, put on music
pau1riddle: Lol it's 2 pm
newtomcroose: hard things for a legend
suurrend3r: put some hardcore music and keep going
newtomcroose: @suurrend3r what about energy drinks :D ?
Bryanswagbeast: some fucking slipknot brother
scriptedp0ison_: put some ytcracker on
suurrend3r: @newtomcroose that will work too
Bryanswagbeast: Sponsored by red bull!
vtcN_: dual core
pau1riddle: i dont like it
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 put some neffex one shot
Bryanswagbeast: wtf is that?
vtcN_: bone thugs n harmony
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
scriptedp0ison_: 😢
suurrend3r: @tomcr00s3 I think a little break drinking coffee will help you
Bryanswagbeast: i rather listen to you play the piano! @tomcr00s3
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 i recommend dua lipa musics for you
suurrend3r: a little break*
pau1riddle: george's IQ is now diminished to that of a cat because of sleep deprivation
newtomcroose: we dont talking about IQ
Bryanswagbeast: surrender!? Please have some manners! Its Break;
pau1riddle: no willpower to execute, just clicking around
newtomcroose: EQ is important
suurrend3r: LUL
scriptedp0ison_: @bryanswagbeast no its "break <ENTER>"
suurrend3r: LUL LUL
suurrend3r: "break n"
scriptedp0ison_: BrokeBack
newtomcroose: I see the moon I see the moon I see the moon Oh, when you're looking at the sun I'm not a fool I'm not a fool I'm not a fool No, you're not fooling anyone
Bryanswagbeast: kill all python lmao
suurrend3r: sudo killall Xorg && rm -rf /
scriptedp0ison_: lol..err..c..aN..t..Ty....p3
newtomcroose: @suurrend3r and hello to the real world :D ?
suurrend3r: geohot it's time to get a real job
newtomcroose: PogChamp PogChamp
suurrend3r: LUL
newtomcroose: what is your mean about real job ? work for google :D ?
pau1riddle: yeah fck this comma ai self driving shit
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL
pau1riddle: go church some jira tickets for ecommerce website
newtomcroose: fck ML coding . just learn php
suurrend3r: "nobodies code in php since 2004" - geohot
Bryanswagbeast: for(int i = 0; i <= twitchViewers.length; i )
newtomcroose: @suurrend3r except facebook
scriptedp0ison_: why not sudo ps -aux | grep "Xorg" | awk -F "pid:" ''
Bryanswagbeast: System.out.println("Hello")
suurrend3r: @newtomcroose facebook got hacked
pau1riddle: because nobody uses grep anymore, it's ripgrep everywhere
scriptedp0ison_: no Java up in here son!
Bryanswagbeast: python then
scriptedp0ison_: @pau1riddle riddle me this why do I still see its usage deployed in professional development environments?
newtomcroose: JUST ASSEMBLY
scriptedp0ison_: lol jk
Bryanswagbeast: oops! gtg! Fornite update out!
suurrend3r: @newtomcroose I think wikipedia is in php too
scriptedp0ison_: @bryanswagbeast eww Cod Blackout is where its at
Bryanswagbeast: html
lolcoolkat: fmt.Println(“Hello”) Kappa
newtomcroose: Knock knock, let the devil in Malevolent as I’ve ever been, head is spinnin’ This medicine’s screamin’, “L-l-l-let us in!” L-l-lick like a salad bowl, Edgar Allen Poe Bedridden, shoulda been dead a long time ago
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose Venom was good
scriptedp0ison_: George play Eminem - Venom
pau1riddle: nooo eminem
newtomcroose: george is not high right now :D
lolcoolkat: watching this is hurting my head WutFace
denim_lap: man I work well to your sound of working
scriptedp0ison_: @lolcoolkat how is the fmt method, redirecting standard in to your teletype device through stdout?
lolcoolkat: what lol
newtomcroose: what lol ? or what is lol :| ?
lolcoolkat: idk what u are asking
scriptedp0ison_: @newtomcroose why you so :Z all the time?
scriptedp0ison_: george get some rest man
newtomcroose: @scriptedp0ison_ because my iq is 2,000
newtomcroose: @scriptedp0ison_ LIFE IS WORK . not rest
suurrend3r: This is like send a post petition without libraries and a lot of captchas Kappa
lolcoolkat: iq is 2000 but your english level is a solid 5 Kappa
newtomcroose: @lolcoolkat because i am a legend Kappa
scriptedp0ison_: @lolcoolkat lol
lolcoolkat: CoolStoryBob
newtomcroose: http://fortune.com/2018/05/05/warren-buffett-elon-musk-trolling-sees-candies-moats/
lolcoolkat: does anyone know whats going on anymore :D
scriptedp0ison_: YTCracker is literally nerdcore/hacker genre music, some of his other songs are better
suurrend3r: I think when Geohot says "life is work", what he is trying to say is that it's not worth work for somebody
suurrend3r: because life is work!
scriptedp0ison_: George much respect for sticking through this
slapusillydawg: my favorite change in python 3 was making parentheses necessary for the print statement, dont fukin @ me
suurrend3r: "i'm just guessing" that's the best part of programming
lolcoolkat: @slapusillydawg Kappa
suurrend3r: the art of guessing
suurrend3r: I didn't know it was that hard bro
scriptedp0ison_: @slapusillydawg no, whats better was the implementation of formated string literals and how PEP8 standardized them
sntboss: i want to be good in c first , there is away to learn fast ?
scriptedp0ison_: @slapusillydawg We don't care for string interpolation anymore
vtcN_: Practice
keepingtrckofthisacct: @sntboss practice
sntboss: any links can help me be good ?
PEREZthe1: @sntboss get off twitch, then practice
slapusillydawg: i see all these people @ing me when i explicitly told them not to and its really giving me anxiety rn if im bein honest
suurrend3r: @sntboss you just gotta code and stop watching live streams Kappa
vtcN_: Pick a thing and write a thing
lolcoolkat: @slapusillydawg Kappa Kappa
sntboss: do u know anygood learning website ?
scriptedp0ison_: @sntboss no C is a very time consuming language to learn as it's closer compiled to the Assembly opcode for your specific CPU architecture
scriptedp0ison_: go with a higher level language such as python, or ruby.
suurrend3r: Here is 06:21 goddamn
lolcoolkat: 5:21 here ResidentSleeper
scriptedp0ison_: its 4:21 am for me
keepingtrckofthisacct: @suurrend3r how long has he been streaming?
vtcN_: 421 for me. Gotta logon at 9...
vtcN_: Working from home is nice
lolcoolkat: better sleep WutFace
scriptedp0ison_: @slapusillydawg what are you talking about?
suurrend3r: im not really sure I think since 01:30
scriptedp0ison_: he's around 4 hours now
scriptedp0ison_: its really impressive because hes so devoted
scriptedp0ison_: how many people can go through this much mental labor and still be disciplined enough to sit through it this long. not many. respect to George for that
lolcoolkat: alot... Kappa
scriptedp0ison_: lol u troll
suurrend3r: @scriptedp0ison_ hedo this once a month
vtcN_: @scriptedp0ison_ on a personal project
FalconJet_: did anyone take his bch
scriptedp0ison_: i know..watch comma.ai archive on YouTube
lolcoolkat: I did :)
beep13: is this just for a learning experience?
scriptedp0ison_: @beep13 that and for fun
scriptedp0ison_: I love watching these streams
lolcoolkat: and to kill his braincells Kappa
keepingtrckofthisacct: is comma.ai completed?
TheHandSolo: George, Im such a long time admire of your work
beep13: yeah i found the youtube stuff yday, now im here =)
suurrend3r: we all love geohot work
lolcoolkat: same came from comma ai archive :D
vtcN_: @beep13 same, it got recommended so i watched his twitchchess stream while working today
FalconJet_: @tomcr00s3 you on a mac or a hackintosh?
suurrend3r: mac
suurrend3r: macbook
lolcoolkat: he’s on Ubuntu rn Kappa
FalconJet_: oh fasho, i see the battery percentage
jotembruv: fucking segwit indeed
suurrend3r: what problem is he fixing now?
beep13: !uptime
twintowerpower: !downtime
beep13: id he just start?
beep13: did*
twintowerpower: nope
jotembruv: hell no
vtcN_: uptime too high, hasn't patched in a while
suurrend3r: he start streaming 5 hours ago
beep13: he is on east coast no?
beep13: what hours this guy sleep lol
twintowerpower: pretty sure he is west coast
suurrend3r: here is when the shitty code start Kappa
suurrend3r: I don't know if I write that right cause my english is not too good brahs
twintowerpower: did you mean to say he's cute as a cat? @suurrend3r
suurrend3r: LUL
suurrend3r: LUL LUL LUL LUL
beep13: west coast it is!
twintowerpower: he's losing hope the only thing that can keep him going is more moneys
Mac_33: i fell asleep
un3okapi: made 10$ in crypto donations at least LUL
suurrend3r: "fuck off" make me laugh
suurrend3r: made*
suurrend3r: @twintowerpower lol
NoPartiesGuy: are there any archives from streams, since I see they are not saved on twitch
suurrend3r: just remember when you hack the ps3, for sure was harder than this
NoPartiesGuy: Maybe it wasn't LUL
TheMartesLive: @NoPartiesGuy comma ai archive on youtube
suurrend3r: I love Twitch and Geohot
suurrend3r: SoBayed
scriptedp0ison_: @tomcr00s3 Amazing stream as always
Jaany: hello george :D
scriptedp0ison_: George you gonna get some rest man
un3okapi: ResidentSleeper
suurrend3r: people who write the protocol should be in jail
suurrend3r: wrote*
suurrend3r: Kappa
myaocat: hi
myaocat: yo its geohot and thoae who dont know im getting sued by sony (dj ton ton)
suurrend3r: tired af
scriptedp0ison_: George get some sleep man
myaocat: can you do some rap
Jaany: sup george :D
myaocat: NEVER GIVE UP!!!
scriptedp0ison_: You did good man lol get some well deserved rest
OPHaru: we tried BibleThump
slapusillydawg: woah you really have the email address lol@lol.com? PogChamp
myaocat: sony gave him
Jaany: LUL
suurrend3r: ResidentSleeper
myaocat: lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE
Jaany: 5hr30m for $10 PogChamp
suurrend3r: thats pretty sick
myaocat: 50% goes for tax
Jaany: 5hr30m for $10 PogChamp
un3okapi: more PogChamp
foxubu: Drink Mate!
myaocat: recursion stream lol
un3okapi: <3
Jaany: <3 take care
myaocat: lupoMEOW lupoMEOW lupoMEOW
suurrend3r: SeemsGood MingLee MingLee MingLee